That's a real thing because I found out that I was codependent.
You know what I'm saying?
Same.
So when you start setting these boundaries, people don't, they don't like it anymore.
No.
They're just like, oh, well, what the f*** are we here for then?
They don't like a boundary, honey.
They don't like a no.
They don't like an expectation, obligation, responsibility.
They like, what's that?
What is that?
You should just be happy I'm here.
And for a long time you were.
Yeah, for sure.
I just, I really was in all areas of my life.
Like, I don't care if it was friend, like a person on the street.
Like I got three kids and I'm helping somebody fold their stroller down and do, you know,
like I just really felt like I have to do extra s*** for people.
I don't know why.
We are very similar.
See.